David J.O. Seitz

Operations/Project Manager

(604) 314-2545

david.jo.seitz@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

I am an Operations/Project Manager with extensive experience coordinating and managing teams. I am familiar with several organizational tools and techniques, and have a proven talent for communicating with customers, thanks to my background in customer service.

KEY SKILLS -

- Highly experienced in managing and delivering customer expectations
- Able to prepare and review business documents
- In-depth knowledge of remote team management tools
- Experience developing teams
- Highly developed communication skills
- Proven ability to identify areas for inside sales
- Skilled at analyzing performance for improvement
- Experience with SaaS and remote teams
- Experience with MS Office

EDUCATION -

Project Management Institute

CAPM Certification

Sonoma State University

- B.A. Theater Arts

EXPERIENCE

May 2019 – January 2020

Customer Service Specialist • ecmarket, inc.

Created and implemented training program • Organized and maintained internal knowledge base.

May 2017 – May 2019

Customer Service Representative • Hush Communications, Inc.

Analyzed and documented necessary growth areas • Worked with multiple departments to guide development.

April 2016 - May 2017

Customer Coordinator • SS&C Advent

Handled high-pressure stakeholder concerns daily • Worked independently and with teams to coordinate issues and resources.

December 2011 - September 2015

Project Coordinator/Team Manager • Berkeley Electronic Press

Designed and implemented project plans • Lead a team to coordinate multiple projects and grow team knowledge.

COMMUNICATION

Wrote and delivered global webinars, including on-the-fly Q&A • Presented plans for growth to internal and external stakeholders • Gathered and disseminated customer success metrics.

LEADERSHIP

Team leader/Manager for team of 4-5 people • Led initiative to address competition's impact on sales • Trained multiple new hires in various roles.

